Jay Aherkar

Pune, Maharashtra, India



jayaherkar@icloud.com



7038312337



linkedin.com/in/jay-aherkar-794296185

Summary

I am a entrepreneur, researcher, and student living in Pune, India. I work at Pranbodhini, striving to develop better healthcare for everyone. Previously I worked in the Dell Technologies as an Business Management Intern and also interned in IBM.

Experience



Co-Founder

Pranbodhini

Jul 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months +)

Pranbodhini aims to create healthy environment for everyone by developing products to reduce bacteria and funguses present in the air.

Business Management Intern

Dell EMC

Jul 2019 - Jan 2020 (7 months)



Product Development Intern

IBM

Oct 2018 - Oct 2018 (1 month)

Education



Fergusson College

High School Diploma, High School

2019 - 2021



Jnana Prabodhini Navanagar Vidyalaya

10th SSC Examination, Higher Education/Higher Education Administration 2016 - 2019

Skills

Project Management • Product Development • Business Analysis • Sales Management • Financial Analysis • Marketing • Social Media • Python (Programming Language) • Management • Communication

Honors & Awards



UNICEF-ATL Young Champion Award - UNICEF

Nov 2018

The awards were presented to the six most innovative solutions from across India, which were shortlisted through the Atal Tinkering Marathon.

TOP INNOVATIONS OF 2017 ATL MARATHON - Dell Technologies

Jan 2019

For innovation of Herbal Spray which can reduce microorganisms in the air. Dell appreciated the concept and awarded for this Innovation.

■ IBM Student Intern - IBM & Niti Aayog

Oct 2018

This award was presented for successful completion of ATL-IBM Under 18 Students Internship in IBM, Bangalore

Honourable Participation in IIF Arerna - India Innovation Forum
Jul 2019